[Road to Success]
[찬여번성: 별처럼 빛나리]
[Episode 21]
[제21화]
Five of characters.
5만
There's something fishy between you two.
둘이 수상해
-We're just in sync. -Hurry.
- 이게 콤비지 - 어서
I'm in such good luck today.
오늘 패가 아주 좋네
Watch it.
자
Pung!
펑
-Good for you. -I just won.
- 괜찮네 - 낫네
And you won big.
대박이네
-You’re so lucky. -Take a bite.
- 운이 정말 좋나 봐 - 또 해
Can't believe you pulled it off.
이런 패로도 나버리고
You're back?
왔니?
Leave him be.
신경 쓰지 마요
Pay up!
돈 내놔요
Chengye, you're back.
청예, 왔니?
Your mom and the others already ate.
다들 식사는 하셨어
I saved some food for you.
네 끼니도 챙겨 놨으니까
Come eat it in a bit.
이따 와서 먹어
Auntie.
아주머니
That thing...
저거
Is it a gift from him again?
또 그 인간이 보낸 거죠?
Finally, a big weight's off my mind.
드디어 큰 문제를 해결해서 후련하네요
Ms. Lin,
린 선생님은
you're not letting things take their own course now?
이럴 때 순리에 맡기지 않나 봐요?
If I keep on that track,
계속 순리에 맡기다가는
I'll be stuck in a rut and achieve nothing.
제자리걸음만 걷고 이뤄지는 게 업잖아요
You took the words right out of my mouth.
내 마음의 소리와 똑같네요
What do you mean, Coach Wang?
그게 무슨 말이에요, 코치님?
We're back on good terms now, aren't we?
우리 이제 화해한 거 맞죠?
Yes, merely.
굳이 말하자면요
We have merely
굳이 말하자면
restored our partnership
이해관계로 맺어진
maintained by mutual interests.
파트너 관계를 회복한 거죠
Is that all?
그게 다예요?
What else do you want?
그럼 뭘 더 바라는데요?
I...
난...
There's a flower shop ahead.
저 앞 꽃집에 가서
I'm going there to buy fertilizer.
비료 좀 사 올게요
♪ Every night ♪
♪ 매일 밤 ♪
I...
난...
♪ I reach for starlight ♪
♪ 나는 손을 뻗어 별빛을 만져 ♪
♪ Wandering through dreams with you ♪
♪ 너와 함께 꿈속을 떠돌며 ♪
♪ I follow the beat of my heart ♪
♪ 심장 박동의 리듬을 따라가 ♪
♪ Like dust floating in the air ♪
♪ 떠도는 먼지처럼 ♪
I know. I know.
나도 알아, 안다고
Do you dare to hit me?
네가 날 칠 수나 있어?
-Coach, Ms. Lin. -Ms. Lin.
- 코치님 - 린 선생님
We just heard from the organizing committee
방금 조직 위원회에서 공지를 받았는데
that our next opponent has been changed to Yongchuan Hengjiu.
다음 경기 상대가 융촨 헝주로 바뀌었대
Yongchuan Hengjiu?
융촨 헝주요?
Are you kidding me?
무슨 말도 안 되는 소리예요?
Weren't we supposed to play Xinpeng?
신펑이랑 붙기로 했잖아요
The students of Xinpeng were informed on a short notice
신펑 학생들이 갑자기 통보를 받았대
of attending an important local event that overlaps
시에서 하는 중요한 행사에 가야 해서
in schedule with the match.
경기 날짜와 겹친다고
As if we weren't already on thin ice.
우리를 탈락시키려고 하늘이 기도하네
What was that gibberish?
무슨 말을 그렇게 해?
Ms. Lin,
린 선생님
they can't just change our opponent, can they?
이렇게 막 바꿔도 되는 거예요?
In the group round-robin,
조별 리그에서는
it's reasonable and compliant with the rules to adjust the sequence
불가항력으로 팀의 경기 순서를 바꾸는 건
of group matches.
규정에 어긋나지 않아
But that doesn't mean they had to replace
그래도 우리 상대를
our original opponent with Yongchuan Hengjiu.
융촨 헝주로 바꾸는 건 아니죠
They scored nine goals in their previous match.
지난번에 걔네는 아홉 골이나 넣었어
Nine goals.
아홉 골이나
Their list of players includes
헝주 스쿼드는
three National Youth Team members.
국가 청소년 대표팀 선수가 세 명이나 있어
One of them is Fang Sulun,
그중 팡쑤룬은
who did a bicycle kick in the box in an earlier match
지난번 일본 청소년 대표팀과의 경기에서
against the Japanese Youth League,
페널티 에어리어에서 바이시클 킥을 날릴 정도로
showcasing superb skills.
기술이 엄청나지
Not to mention Qin Qiechu.
친체추는 말할 것도 없어
Everyone on the online forum
커뮤니티에서는
says he's being groomed
국가 대표팀
as a key reserve player for the national team.
예비 주전 선수로 키운다고 하더라고
Wait.
아니
Do you have to throw a wet blanket
꼭 이럴 때
on everyone at a time like this?
찬물을 끼얹어야겠어요?
I'm just stating the facts.
팩트만 말한 것뿐이야
Fragility is not to be denied.
레벨을 인정해야지
Enough, the two of you.
그만해
Coach.
코치님은
What's your opinion?
어떻게 생각하세요?
What opinion can I have?
어떻게 생각하긴
You all did a good job on the analysis.
다들 분석을 제대로 했잖아
I was not asking you about that.
그거 말고요
I meant our chances of defeating Yongchuan Hengjiu.
저희가 융촨 헝주랑 붙어서 이길 확률이요
The chances are slim,
승산은 거의 없어
but there is still hope.
그래도 희망은 있지
I think you should just eat and sleep well,
내 생각엔 밥 잘 먹고, 잠 잘 자고
and get onto the field with a calm mind.
평정심을 갖고 경기에 임하는 게 중요해
Go home and rest early.
얼른 가서 쉬어
Conserve your energy.
체력 아껴 뒀다가
Try your best in tomorrow's match.
내일 경기 잘 치러야지
Okay.
네
Can't believe we'll play Hengjiu.
헝주랑 붙다니
This is so stressful.
부담된다
Bye bye.
- 잘 가
Just take the coach's advice.
코치님 말씀대로
Eat and drink as usual.
밥 잘 먹고, 잘 자면 돼
I probably won't be able to sleep tonight.
난 오늘 밤에 잠은 다 잤어
You make it sound like you could do it.
그런다고 달라질 건 없어
Off you go. We'll walk together next time.
먼저 가 다음에 같이 가자
Okay, I'm leaving then.
- 알았어 - 먼저 간다
-Bye. -I'm leaving too. Bye.
- 잘 가
Goodbye, Ms. Lin.
선생님, 안녕히 가세요
Goodbye, Coach.
코치님, 안녕히 가세요
Fu, shall we?
가자, 푸신수
Sure.
가자
Anything wrong?
왜 그래?
Did you lose anything?
뭐 잃어버렸어?
I can't find my keychain.
열쇠고리가 안 보여
The one with that utterly ugly jersey, right?
그 엄청 못생긴 유니폼 말이야?
If it's gone, just let it be.
그냥 잊어버려
That stuff's tacky after all, right?
어차피 촌스러운 거잖아
Fu Xinshu!
푸신수
-Fu Xinshu, look what time it is now. -No, I must find it.
- 이미 늦었어 - 안 돼, 두고는 못 가
I'll buy you a new one tomorrow.
내가 내일 새로 사 줄게
Let's go grab a bite first.
일단 나랑 야식이나 먹으러 가자
Come on. Let's go.
어서 가자
Hey, kids.
얘들아
Let's go watch cartoons.
우리 만화 보러 가자
Come on, kids.
꼬마야
Kids, time to watch cartoons.
얘들아, 우리 만화 보러 가자
Hey, kiddo?
얘들아
Everyone's here, right?
다 모였지?
Yiling, come on.
이링도 어서 가자
Why didn't you go watch cartoons with the others?
넌 왜 친구들이랑 영화 보러 안 가?
I don't know them.
난 쟤들 몰라
Don't you want to get to know them?
친해지고 싶지도 않아?
I've seen you staying
너 혼자 병실에 있는 거
in your ward alone several times.
매번 봤었는데
Where are your parents?
네 부모님은?
They didn't come see me.
아무도 안 오셨어
Do you play football?
너 축구 할 줄 알아?
I just joined the school team this semester.
나 이번 학기에 학교 대표로 들어갔거든
Let's go play football together.
우리 같이 축구 하러 가자
But we're in a hospital now.
근데 여긴 병원이잖아
It doesn't matter.
괜찮아
I have a big secret hideout.
나한테 엄청 큰 비밀기지가 있거든
Come with me.
가자
Don't keep yourself in the ward all the time.
맨날 병실에만 있지 말고
Basking in the sun outside
나가서 햇볕도 좀 쬐야
more often will help you recover faster.
병도 빨리 낫지
My name is Fu Xinshu.
내 이름은 푸신수야
What's yours?
넌 이름이 뭐야?
My dad doesn't like me.
우리 아빠는 날 안 좋아해
And I hate being his son.
나도 그 인간의 아들이 되기도 싫고
So I don't have a name.
그래서 난 이름이 없어
I'll call you Bed No. 4 then.
그럼 내가 널 4호 침대라고 부를게
Let's go play football, Bed No. 4.
4호 침대야 축구하러 가자
Quick!
빨리 와, 빨리
I'll go get the ball.
내가 가서 공 가져올게
Bed No. 4,
4호 침대
today, I'll teach you how to
오늘 내가 어떻게 하면
precisely get hold of the ball.
공을 정확하게 찰 수 있는지 알려 줄게
Okay.
알았어
Bed No. 4.
4호 침대
♪ Who hasn't known the dark of night and uncertainty? ♪
♪ 누구나 어둠과 방황의 시간을 지나 ♪
You stay right here.
넌 거기 있어
You're still in recovery.
아직 다 안 나았으니까
[Dangerous zone; Do not climb]
[위험한 구역 올라가지 마시오]
Do be careful.
조심히 차
Got it.
알았어
♪ Stumbling, covered in wounds, losing direction ♪
♪ 넘어지고 상처투성이가 되며 방향을 잃은 채 ♪
Very good.
잘했어
♪ Wandering alone, gaining strength through pain ♪
♪ 홀로 헤매지만 그렇게 강해지는 법이야 ♪
[Dangerous zone; Do not climb]
[위험한 구역 올라가지 마시오]
♪ Riding the wind, chasing an unknown horizon ♪
♪ 바람을 타고 미지의 내일을 향해 달려가 ♪
♪ Looking up, dreaming side by side of great ideals ♪
♪ 고개를 들어 원대한 꿈을 간직한 채 ♪
♪ The vast world awaits youth to arrive ♪
♪ 드넓은 세상에 우린 거침없이 뛰어들 거야 ♪
Fu Xinshu, this is no fun at all.
푸신수 너 너무 힘 없게 찬다
♪ If facing every storm is ♪
♪ 거센 풍파를 용감하게 마주하는 것만이 ♪
Let's both take a few steps back.
좀 더 멀리 갈 테니까
You should kick harder.
더 세게 차 봐
♪ What it takes to grow ♪
♪ 성장이라고 한다면 ♪
Over here.
여기로 패스해
Catch it.
받아
♪ I will stubbornly go against the current ♪
♪ 난 기꺼이 그곳에서 ♪
Now, pass it to me.
패스한다
Okay.
알았어
♪ And let myself go wild ♪
♪ 뜨겁게 싸워 볼 거야 ♪
Catch this one. Here it goes!
잘 받아
♪ No matter how long the road ahead ♪
♪ 미래가 멀다 해도 ♪
♪ Nothing can stop me ♪
♪ 내 질주는 멈추지 않아 ♪
♪ Break through every haze of doubt ♪
♪ 모든 방황을 부수며 ♪
♪ Chase the light within me ♪
♪ 나만의 빛을 쫓아가 ♪
♪ Strong wings grow through the storm ♪
♪ 풍파 속에서 끝내 강인한 날개를 펼칠 테니까 ♪
[Fu Xinshu] [Bed No. 4]
[푸신수] [4번 침대]
♪ Even if no one cheers ♪
♪ 모두가 날 외면해도 ♪
Come on, pass it over!
여기로 패스해
♪ I'll keep fighting my way through ♪
♪ 힘을 다해 싸울 거야 ♪
There it goes.
받아
Okay!
알았어
P-Pass the ball to me.
다시 나한테 패스해
♪ On a deserted battlefield ♪
♪ 아무도 없는 경기장에서 ♪
Pass it now!
패스
♪ Thrive and bloom ♪
♪ 당당하게 성장해 ♪
♪ I'll take every scar ♪
♪ 모든 상처를 ♪
♪ As my badge of honor ♪
♪ 영광의 훈장으로 삼을 거야 ♪
Pass the ball!
패스, 패스
You've got this! Shoot!
좋았어, 슛
Bed No. 4.
4호 침대
You'll be discharged soon, right?
너 곧 퇴원하지?
Fu Xinshu, thanks for teaching me how to play football.
푸신수 축구를 가르쳐줘서 고마워
It looks cute.
이거 진짜 귀엽다
I'll hang it on my backpack.
내 가방에 달고 다닐게
Then you must never take it off.
절대 떼면 안 돼
Bed No. 4,
4번 침대
you're about to leave the hospital,
곧 퇴원하는데
yet I still don't know your name.
네 이름도 모르고 우리 헤어지는 거야?
Well, then meet me next week
그럼 다음 주에
on my birthday at that fried chicken place.
내 생일 때 치킨집에서 만나면
I'll tell you when you get there.
그때 꼭 알려 줄게
Okay. I'll definitely be there.
그래, 꼭 갈게
Great.
좋아
Come on.
약속
-Pinky swear.
새끼손가락 걸고
-No backsies.
100년 동안 약속 지키기
I promised a classmate
친구랑 약속했어요
to spend my birthday with him.
그 친구랑 같이 생일을 보내기로 했어요
No, you can't go.
안 돼
You have to spend this birthday
이번 생일은 반드시
with your grandparents.
할아버지, 할머니랑 같이 보내
We are moving to Yongchuan soon.
곧 융촨으로 이사 가니까
Why are we moving?
왜 이사 가요?
To start a new company— at least it appears so.
회사를 설립해서 이사한다곤 하지만
But in fact,
사실
it's just to make it easier
네 아빠가 편하게
for your dad to meet with his side piece.
그 불여우 같은 걸 만나려고 이사하는 거란다
Hu Yongping!
후융핑
Why did you have to speak nonsense when our son's around?
애 앞에서 무슨 말도 안 되는 소리야?
What did I do wrong?
내가 틀린 말 했어?
Spare me that crap.
쓸데없는 소리 집어치워
You want to dump me, huh?
이렇게 날 버리게?
I'm telling you, not a chance.
꿈도 꾸지 마
Shut that filthy mouth of yours!
그 주둥이 안 닥쳐?
I want to go to...
갈 거예요
You shut it too!
너도 조용해
Listen up, sign the papers
잘 들어
if you want a divorce.
이혼하고 싶으면 도장 찍어
Why can't I speak?
내가 왜 닥쳐야 하는데?
Retain what little shame you have.
적당히 해
-You may have it, but I still do! -I'm not going to divorce you.
- 참는 데 한계가 있으니까 - 나도 이혼할 생각 없어
-Chengye! -You stay put!
- 청예 - 거기 앉아
Chengye!
청예
Where are you going?
어디 가는데?
Come back here, Chengye!
돌아와, 청예
Chengye!
청예
Chengye, come back!
청예, 돌아와
Never ever come back if you dare run away!
그렇게 갔다가 다시 올 생각도 하지 마
You should've watched out.
조심하렴
Little boy,
얘야
are you okay?
괜찮니?
I'm fine.
괜찮아요
[Available all day on workdays] [Breakfast deals]
[상시 운영] [모닝 세트]
Thank God I'm not late.
다행이다, 안 늦었네
Come on, get some fries.
- 감자튀김 먹자 - 감자튀김
What a spread.
많다
Help yourself to whatever you like.
먹고 싶은 거 마음껏 먹어
Has he forgotten our pact?
잊은 건가?
How is it? Is it good?
어때, 맛있니?
Yes.
맛있어요
No vacant tables.
자리 없다
Go ask that boy.
가서 물어봐
Hey, little one,
꼬마야
can we swap seats with you?
우리 자리 좀 바꿔 줄 수 있어?
Sure.
네
-Thank you. -Thanks.
고마워
What would you like to eat?
뭐 먹을래?
What about you two?
뭐 먹고 싶어?
Here comes the birthday cake!
생일 케이크다
Happy birthday!
생일 축하한다
Happy birthday to you.
생일 축하합니다
Bed No. 4, you're about to leave the hospital,
4호 침대, 곧 퇴원하는데
yet I still don't know your name.
네 이름도 모르고 우리 헤어지는 거야?
Well, then meet me next week
그럼 다음 주에
on my birthday at that fried chicken place.
내 생일 때 치킨집에서 만나면
I'll tell you when you get there.
그때 꼭 알려 줄게
Okay, I will definitely be there.
그래, 꼭 갈게
-Pinky swear. No backsies.
새끼손가락 걸고 100년 동안 약속 지키기
Hello, it's our child's birthday today.
오늘 아이가 생일이라서
We'd like to offer you a cup of ice cream.
저희 아이스크림을 나눠드리고 있습니다
Hey, little one,
꼬마야
a free cup of ice cream for you.
너도 아이스크림 줄게
-Thank you. -Here you are, a spoon.
- 고맙습니다 - 숟가락도 받으렴
It's our child's birthday.
오늘 아이가 생일이라서
-We'd like to share the joy with you. -Thanks.
- 저희 아이스크림을 - 고맙습니다
Look, here's ice cream.
나눠드리고 있습니다
Come on.
받으세요
-Here you are. -You got one yet?
- 받아 - 받았어?
Are you having fun?
기분 좋지?
A spoon for you.
숟가락
[KFC]
[치킨집]
Little boy, you've been sitting here alone the entire day.
꼬마야, 혼자서 하루 종일 여기 앉아 있는 거니?
Where are your parents?
부모님은 어디 계셔?
We're closing the place.
우리 이제 문 닫아야 하거든
[KFC]
[치킨집]
Never ever come back if you dare run away!
그렇게 갔다가 다시 올 생각도 하지 마
Now you get it.
이제 알았니?
You're nothing
우리 집안을 떠나면
when you're out of the Wen family.
넌 아무것도 아니야
Finish it and go home.
다 먹고 집에 가자
If you're not eating it, put it away and get up!
안 먹을 거면 그냥 치우고 일어나
Wen Chengye, how come you're still here?
원청예, 아직 안 갔어?
Why did you come back?
왜 다시 왔어?
Don't get me started.
말도 마
I lost something really important.
내가 아주 중요한 물건을 잃어버렸거든
I must find it back.
꼭 찾아야 하는 거라서
So you found it?
네가 주웠구나
Thank you.
고마워
Is it very important to you?
이게 너한테 그렇게 중요해?
I made someone a promise
다른 사람이랑 약속했거든
that I'd never take it off.
절대 안 빼겠다고
Why the laugh?
왜 웃어?
It really is of great importance to me.
나한테는 엄청 중요한 거라고
Is that so?
그래?
If it truly meant so much to you,
그렇게 중요했으면서
how could you not recognize me?
왜 날 못 알아보는 거야?
Bed No. 4...
4번 침대가...
You are Bed No. 4?
네가 4번 침대였어?
Drop the act.
됐어
Don't pretend like you still remember me.
잊지 않은 척하지 마
I do remember you.
안 잊었어
How could I have forgotten? I...
내가 어떻게 잊겠어?
I've always wanted to find you
계속 널 다시 찾고 싶었어
and play football with you again.
너랑 다시 같이 축구하고 싶었다고
You were my very first best friend.
넌 내 첫 번째 친구니까
Then why didn't you come meet me?
근데 왜 안 왔어?
We made a pinky promise
우리 새끼손가락 걸고
that you'd celebrate my birthday with me.
내 생일을 같이 보내기로 약속했잖아
I waited for you for a whole day.
하루 종일 널 기다렸어
Why?
왜?
Why on earth didn't you show up?
도대체 왜 안 왔냐고
I'll ask you one last time.
마지막으로 묻는다
Why?
왜 안 왔어?
I don't want to say it.
말하고 싶지 않아
Think whatever you want.
네 맘대로 생각해
I just don't want to say it.
말하기 싫으니까
Fu!
푸신수
Wen Chengye, what's wrong with you?
원청예 너 지금 뭐 하는 거야?
-You fancy a beating or what? -Qin Ao!
- 봐주니까 선 넘냐? - 친아오
Come watch this video.
와서 영상 좀 봐
Fu!
푸신수
This needle of yours
게이지가
is already... off track.
움직이지 시작하더니 방향을 틀었어
Where is it pointing at?
- 어딜 가리키는 거야? - 여기
We could've had some more time
최종 보스를 이렇게 빨리
before playing the strongest opponent.
만나지 않아도 됐었는데
No need to look at the points table anymore.
순위표는 이제 안 봐도 돼요
Yongchuan Hengjiu will surely defeat all their opponents
융촨 헝주는 분명 모든 상대를 이기고
and advance as the first in the group.
조 1위로 진출할 거니까
But yesterday, didn't you say there was still hope?
어제는 희망이 있다고 했잖아요
Given our players' state now, they might even
지금 애들 상태로
have problems coordinating with each other in today's match.
오늘 경기에서 호흡을 맞추는 것도 문제일 거예요
That said, Yongchuan Hengjiu is the strongest opponent
하지만 융촨 헝주는 지금 단계에서
we can meet in the current stage.
만날 수 있는 가장 강한 상대니까
Even if we lose simply because they're better,
설령 실력 차이로 진다고 해도
at least our players get to enjoy the game itself.
애들은 경기 자체를 즐길 수 있을 텐데
So, why not take a positive attitude
왜 의미 있는 패배를
to embracing a meaningful defeat,
기대하면 안 되는 거죠?
Ms. Lin?
린 선생님
The bus is here.
차 왔다
Get on it, guys.
어서 타라
-Okay. -Coming right up.
- 네 - 갈게요
Let's go.
가자
[Youth Football Super League]
[유소년 축구 슈퍼 리그]
Pretty fancy, isn't it?
여기 진짜 화려하다
So posh.
엄청 화려해
Even the stadium hosting the game between us
융촨 헝주랑 경기하니까
and Yongchuan Hengjiu is different.
경기장 시설도 다르네
What a fancy lounge.
라커룸도 엄청 고급스럽다
I'm even more nervous now.
더 긴장된다
When will the football field
우리 학교 축구장도
in our school have facilities like these?
언제쯤 이렇게 되려나?
Hello, miss.
안녕하세요
My name is Qin Qiechu.
저는 친체추라고 해요
Hello.
그래, 안녕
Coach!
코치님
Coach Winfred,
윈프레드 코치님
I finally get to see you.
드디어 여기서 만나네요
I've always been a huge fan of yours.
저 코치님 왕팬이에요
Why did you abandon our team?
왜 저희 팀을 들었다 놨다 하시는 거예요?
So, this boy is...
그럼 저 친구가...
Yes.
맞아요
He is Qin Qiechu from Yongchuan Hengjiu.
얘가 융촨 헝주의 친체추예요
You actually know who I am, Coach!
절 기억하셨네요
I'm so touched.
진짜 감동이에요
Previously, you said you'd coach our team,
예전에 저희 팀 맡으러 오신다고 하셨었는데
but you didn't.
결국 안 오셨잖아요
After coaching them through this match,
그럼 이번에 얘네 맡고 나면
will you join our team?
저희 팀으로 오시는 거예요?
Bro,
야
don't you think you're rude,
너 좀 무례하다
for calling another team's coach "Coach"?
저분이 네 코치님이냐?
You're Qin Ao!
친아오
I love the way you penetrate into the box!
네 페널티 에어리어 드리블 진짜 잘하더라
Will you give me an autograph?
사인 좀 해 줘
Just sign your name right here.
여기, 여기에다
Here, huh?
여기에 하라고?
T-To be honest,
솔직히 말해
if you become a star player in the future,
나중에 스타 선수가 되려면
such handwriting won't do.
그렇게 사인하면 안 돼
A star player?
스타 선수?
Me?
내가?
You're Fu Xinshu, right?
푸신수 맞지?
You work with Chen Jianghe in a quite interesting way.
너랑 천장허 호흡이 찰떡이더라
Thanks.
고마워
Hello! Hello.
- 안녕
Qi Liang! Nice to meet you.
치량이지? 안녕
And you're Feng Suo, right?
펑쒀 맞지?
You're quite a solid player.
너 꽤 안정적이더라
Well...
그...
I-I have to go now,
나 이제 가 볼게
or my captain will scold me.
주장한테 혼나거든
S-See you later then.
그럼 이따 보자
See you!
이따 봐
See you in a bit.
이따 보자
Bye!
잘 있어
Guys,
얘들아
Qin Qiechu is quite a people person, isn't he?
저 친체추 너무 친한 척하는 거 아니야?
He knows us so well.
우리에 대해 너무 잘 아는데
I have a bad feeling about it.
불길한 예감이 들어
Stop it.
그만들 해
Keep your feelings to yourself.
벌써부터 감 떨어지는 소리 하네
The game hasn't started yet.
시작도 하기 전에
No more pessimistic talk like that.
왜 벌써 김을 빼?
We won't know what they've got until we fight them.
실력은 붙어 봐야 아는 거야
That's right.
맞아
Plus, the fact that our opponent
게다가 상대가 우릴 중요하게 생각한다는 건
takes us seriously means we're not half bad.
우리 실력도 만만치 않다는 거잖아
Exactly.
그래
Alright. It's time to get ready.
그럼 이제 준비하자
Go get changed now.
다들 옷 갈아입어
-Okay. -Got it.
- 네
-Let's go. -Time to get changed.
- 가자 - 유니폼 갈아입자
Everyone in the audience, welcome to the Youth Super League live match.
시청자 여러분, 이곳은 유소년 슈퍼 리그 현장입니다
Today, the match will be held
이번 경기에서 맞붙을 팀은
[Yongchuan Provincial Youth Super League]
[융촨 유소년 슈퍼 리그]
between Yongchuan Hengjiu and Hongjing No. 8 High School.
융촨 헝주와 훙징 제8고등학교입니다
[Hongjing No. 8 High School versus Yongchuan Hengjiu]
[훙징 제8고 대 융촨 헝주]
I believe you're all familiar with Yongchuan Hengjiu.
융촨 헝주는 다들 잘 아시겠지만
It's the reigning five-time champion of the Youth Super League.
유소년 슈퍼 리그 5연패를 달성한 절대 강자입니다
Joined by star players like No. 10, Qin Qiechu,
팀에는 등번호 10번 친체추 선수와
and No. 7, Fang Sulun, it's fair to say
7번 팡쑤룬 선수 등 스타급 선수들이 포진해 있죠
this team is the undisputed king of the pitch.
그야말로 그라운드의 제왕이라고 할 수 있습니다
Most football fans
축구 팬들은 보편적으로
believe that no one can defeat
이번 대회에서
this team in the ongoing tournament.
그들을 이길 팀은 아무도 없다고 생각하실 겁니다
On the other hand,
한편 훙징 제8고등학교는
for their classic free-kick strategy in the match
위저우 인샹과의 경기에서 보여 준
against Yuzhou Yinxiang, Hongjing No. 8 High School
환상적인 프리킥 전술로
is hailed as the dark horse of this tournament.
이번 대회의 다크호스로 떠올랐습니다
Now, the dark horse has stepped onto the king's territory.
이제 다크호스가 왕의 영토에 발을 들였는데요
Who will emerge victorious?
과연 승자는 누가 될지
Let's see what will unfold before our eyes.
함께 지켜보시죠
The two teams' captains
양 팀 주장이
are exchanging pennants.
팀 페넌트를 교환합니다
The pre-match coin toss is complete.
경기 전 동전 던지기로 진영 선택을 마치고
The game is about to start.
경기가 곧 시작되겠습니다
Yongchuan Hengjiu!
융촨 헝주
-We've got this!
- 파이팅
Hongjing No. 8 High School!
훙징 제8고등학교
Right from the kickoff,
경기가 시작되자마자
Hengjiu has shown dominant control over the pitch,
헝주가 강력한 경기 장악력을 보여줍니다
and is suppressing Hongjing in the midfield.
중앙 지역에서 훙징을 압박하고 있습니다
Their 4-3-3 Formation
그들의 4-3-3 포메이션은
is working pretty smoothly,
아주 매끄럽게 운영되고 있는데
with seamless coordination.
호흡이 척척 잘 맞네요
Hengjiu's captain, Player No. 7, Fang Sulun, is dribbling
헝주팀의 주장 등번호 7번 팡쑤룬 선수가
past the opponent's defense.
공을 몰고 돌파합니다
Defense!
수비해
-Defense! -He sold the opposing defenders
- 페인트 동작으로 - 수비해
-with a feint. -Defense!
- 수비수를 제친 후
Then he passes the ball to a midfielder.
중앙으로 공을 패스합니다
The latter,
중앙에 있던 선수가
without stopping the ball,
공을 멈추지 않고
passes it right back to Fang Sulun.
다시 팡쑤룬 선수에게 연결합니다
-No. 10 bursts through the right flank. -Qin Ao, to the right!
- 우측으로 과감하게 돌파 후 - 친아오, 오른쪽이야
He's about to enter the box!
페널티 에어리어로 진입합니다
This kick looks like both a pass and a shoot.
크로스 같은 슈팅인데
Feng Suo fails to catch the ball.
펑쒀 선수가 공을 잡지 못했습니다
No. 10 comes up and shoots again.
따라 들어오던 10번 선수가 슈팅으로
It's a goal!
골망을 흔듭니다
Qin Qiechu
친체추 선수입니다
scored a goal right after the game started.
경기가 시작되자마자
One to zero!
1 대 0입니다
Bravo! Well done!
좋아, 잘했어
Yongchuan Hengjiu is now taking the lead.
융촨 헝주가 기선을 제압합니다
As expected of Qin Qiechu, a star player of Hengjiu,
친체추 선수는 역시 헝주의 에이스 선수답군요
he has put on a brilliant performance.
역시 놀라운 실력을 보여 줍니다
Move!
가자
In less than five minutes after the game started,
경기가 시작된 지 5분도 채 되지 않았는데
Yongchuan Hengjiu got a grip of the match's pace
융촨 헝주가 경기 흐름을 주도하며
and scored the first goal.
선제골을 넣었습니다
Now, for Hongjing,
훙징 제8고는
the priority
지금 전열을 가다듬고
is to steady themselves.
다시 출발해야 합니다
-After all, there's still plenty of time. -Keep your composure, guys!
- 아직 경기 시간을 봤을 때 - 다들 진정해
They still stand a chance of tying
동점을 만들 기회는 충분하고
or even surpassing their opponent.
역전까지도 노려볼 수 있습니다
Hongjing is trying to steady the pace through passing,
훙징이 패스를 통해 흐름을 안정시키고
while seeking a chance to attack.
공격 기회를 엿보고 있습니다
But Hengjiu is pressing aggressively on the pitch.
하지만 헝주의 압박이 굉장히 거셉니다
Such intense pressing
이런 압박 스타일의 플레이는
is giving Hongjing a very hard time.
훙징을 아주 힘들게 할 겁니다
Now, the ball is with Hongjing's captain,
지금 훙징에서 공을 잡은 선수는
Player No. 10, Fu Xinshu.
주장인 등번호 10번 푸신수 선수입니다
That through ball is intercepted!
스루 패스 기회를 차단당했습니다
They're even well aware of Fu Xinshu's
푸신수의 패스 습관까지
passing patterns.
훤히 꿰고 있어요
Hengjiu disrupts the pass and gets the ball.
헝주팀이 한발 앞서 공을 가로챕니다
Now, the ball is with...
지금 공을 잡은 선수는
Player No. 10 of Hengjiu, Qin Qiechu.
헝주팀의 10번 친체추 선수입니다
With excellent skills, he has dribbled past
개인 능력으로
several opposing players in a row.
연속 돌파합니다
Facing the defense being put up by Hongjing,
수비로 복귀한 훙징 선수들을 앞에 두고
a teammate of his quickly breaks through from the right.
오른쪽에 동료 선수가 빠르게 쇄도하고 있습니다
You want to pass the ball? Not a chance!
크로스를 내주지 않을 거야
Qin Qiechu doesn't
친체추 선수
pass the ball to the right flank,
오른쪽으로 패스하지 않고
but to the midfield with a backheel.
힐패스로 중앙에 연결합니다
A shoot!
슛
Here comes one more goal!
또 골입니다
Good anticipation, but we prepared two plans.
예측은 좋았는데 우리도 플랜 B는 있어
Yongchuan is showing
융촨의 팀워크가
much better teamwork than Hongjing!
훙징보다 훨씬 뛰어나네요
That attack
이번 공격은
was a textbook example of teamwork.
그야말로 교과서적인 플레이였습니다
Yongchuan Hengjiu
융촨 헝주가
just scored another goal.
다시 1점을 추가합니다
Now, it's 2-0 on the field.
현재 스코어 2 대 0
Conceding two goal consecutively soon after the game started
경기가 시작되자마자 연달아 두 골을 허용하면서
might shake
훙징 선수들의
the mentality
멘탈이
of Hongjing's players.
흔들릴 수 있겠습니다
Hengjiu's players are too agile.
헝주 애들이 너무 유연해
Can't believe no one on our team fills the gap.
우리 중에 빈자리를 메우는 사람이 아무도 없잖아
Time is pressing.
이러다 망치겠어
I'll do that then!
내가 막자
Player No. 11 of Hongjing, Wen Chengye,
훙징의 11번 원청예 선수가
seems to have left his position in defense
자신의 수비 위치를 벗어나
for the attacking half, fighting for the ball.
전방 압박을 시작합니다
Is it a new strategy of Hongjing's?
이게 훙징의 새로운 전략일까요?
Wen Chengye left his defensive zone.
원청예 선수가 자신의 수비 구역을 벗어났습니다
Wen Chengye, what are you doing?
원청예, 너 뭐 해?
Not only did he fail to steal the ball,
공을 뺏기는커녕
but he also occupied the same position
오히려 수비로 복귀하던 동료 선수와
with a teammate tracking back,
위치가 겹치면서
causing a gap in the defense.
수비에 공백이 생겼습니다
Wen Chengye,
원청예
where are you going?
어디 가는 거야?
That defensive error shouldn't have
완전히 불필요한
happened.
수비 실책이네요
Wen Chengye
원청예 선수
-is marking Qin Qiechu one-on-one again. -Bring it on.
- 친체추 선수를 마크하는데 - 뚫어 봐
Qin Qiechu seizes the chance
친체추 선수가 기회를 놓치지 않고
to break through.
돌파에 성공합니다
He then passes the ball to his captain, Player No. 7,
주장인 7번 선수에게 패스
Fang Sulun, who volleys hard!
팡쑤룬 선수의 강력한 슈팅
The ball hits a defender's leg,
공이 수비수 다리에 맞고
deflects, and finds the net!
굴절되고 골망을 가릅니다
Three to zero!
3 대 0입니다
You alone can't turn the tables.
너 혼자서는 안 돼
Wen Chengye, what was that mess about?
원청예, 경기 망치려고 그래?
Isn't the game a mess already?
이미 망가진 경기야
Hongjing's No. 11 is a real headache.
저 11번 꽤 성가시지 않아?
It's okay. Just try to avoid him.
괜찮아 일단 쟤는 최대한 피해
Yongchuan Hengjiu's passing is rather smooth.
융촨 헝주의 패스 플레이가 물 흐르듯 자연스럽습니다
After scoring the third goal,
현재 3 대 0으로 앞서면서
they've completely taken control of the pace on the field,
경기 흐름을 완전히 장악했는데요
and are bombarding
훙징의 골문을 향해
Hongjing's goal.
맹공을 퍼붓고 있습니다
Another link-up play in a small area.
또다시 짧은 패스로 연계 플레이를 합니다
Then a long shot from outside the box.
페널티 에어리어 외곽에서 중거리 슛
Hongjing's defense is almost collapsing.
훙징의 수비 라인이 거의 무너졌습니다
This time, a penetration through the midfield.
이번에는 중앙으로 직선 침투합니다
The ball goes to the left flank.
공을 왼쪽으로 넘겨주고
The player gently slots it home with his right foot.
오른발로 가볍게 밀어 넣습니다
Four to zero!
4 대 0입니다
Yongchuan Hengjiu extended their lead again
융촨 헝주가 계속해서 압박을 가하며
with relentless pressing.
점수 차를 또 벌리네요
How could this happen?
어떻게 이럴 수가
This happens
선수들, 경기력, 공까지
when all the conditions
모두 우리 편이 아닐 땐
are against us.
결과가 이럴 수밖에 없어요
Yu Ming pulled
위밍 선수
and gave away a foul.
푸싱 파울입니다
-The referee showed him a yellow card. -No. 5, that was a foul.
- 위밍 선수 경고를 받습니다 - 5번 선수 경고입니다
Hengjiu Team gets a free kick in the final third.
헝주가 앞선에서 세트피스 기회를 얻습니다
-It's okay. -Come here!
- 괜찮아 - 빨리 와
-No biggie. -Form a wall.
- 수비벽 세우자
-All is fine. -It's okay.
- 괜찮아
A free kick in a good position around the box.
프리킥 위치가 좋습니다
Will Hongjing keep this one out?
훙징이 막아낼 수 있을까요?
Will Hengjiu further widen the gap by scoring one more goal?
헝주가 점수 차를 더 벌릴지 지켜봐야겠습니다
Lu, stay on him.
린루, 압박해
The ball!
볼 막아
Yongchuan Hengjiu
융촨 헝주
actually adopted Hongjing's tactic
지난 경기 훙징의
on free kicks from the previous match!
프리킥 전술을 그대로 재현했습니다
Player No. 19 in the offside position
오프사이드 위치에 있던
didn't take the ball.
19번 선수가 공을 받지 않고
Instead, he let it slip through
살짝 흘려 주면서
to Player No. 7, his captain,
주장인 7번 선수가
-who scored with a shot into the corner. -Shame on them for copying our tactic.
- 득정에 성공합니다 - 우리 스타일을 따라해?
Five to zero!
5 대 0입니다
-It's a huge blow to Hongjing's morale. -Put in more effort!
- 훙징의 멘탈이 무너지겠군요 - 할 수 있어
You've got this!
힘내
Run forward!
앞으로 뛰어
Qin Ao!
친아오
-There's a good chance! -A good chance!
- 찬스다
Pass it back!
돌아가, 돌아가
-Qin Ao! -Over here!
- 친아오 - 이쪽이야
Okay!
알았어
This is a great opportunity!
찬스다
We can't lose one more score.
더는 실점하면 안 돼
We can see now
보시는 것처럼
Player No. 11 of Hongjing, Wen Chengye,
훙징의 11번 원청예 선수가
is still pressing hard non-stop in the middle and attacking thirds.
계속해서 미드필드와 최전방을 오가며 압박하고 있지만
Unfortunately, he's just running in an extensive area
넓은 범위를 커버하는 움직임으로는
without a clear target.
역부족입니다
Player No. 11 of Hongjing stole the ball
훙징 11번 선수가 가로채기에 성공합니다
by fooling Qin Qiechu with a fake.
페인트 동작으로 친체추 선수를 제치고
He's now dribbling the ball forward.
계속해서 공을 몰고 나갑니다
Hengjiu is in hot pursuit of him.
헝주가 바짝 추격하는데요
Both sides are battling fiercely for the ball in the midfield.
양 팀이 미드필드에서 치열한 몸싸움을 벌입니다
Such a shame.
정말 아쉽네요
Player No. 11 of Hongjing fell.
훙징 11번 선수는
-Are you okay? -Although he has outstanding skills,
- 개인 능력이 뛰어나지만 - 괜찮아?
football requires teamwork after all.
축구는 결국 팀 게임입니다
Without team support on the field,
경기장에서 팀원들의 협력 없이는
individual brilliance amounts to nothing.
혼자서는 역부족이죠
Wen Chengye, what are you so arrogant about?
원청예 왜 폭주하고 난리야?
Why put on airs?
네가 그렇게 잘났어?
Enough, Qin Ao.
진정해, 친아오
I'm mad at him. What were you doing?
솔직히 너 마음에 안 들어
Moving from the defensive half to the midfield,
수비 지역에서 중앙으로
serving as a midfielder to a forward, huh?
중앙에서 최전방까지
Play or get off the pitch.
치고 나가서 뭐 하게?
Do you even know how to pass?
패스할 줄 몰라?
Alright, stop it.
그만해
They're having a mental breakdown.
멘탈이 무너졌나 봐요
So is Wen Chengye.
원청예도 무너지긴 했지만
But at least he's clear-minded.
목표 의식은 뚜렷한 거 같아요
Yes. At least he's still trying.
맞아요 적어도 노력은 하니까요
But it won't be of help.
근데 소용없어요
Wen Chengye has absolutely
원청예는
no intention to cooperate with his teammates,
팀원들이랑 협력할 생각이 전혀 없거든요
who have no idea what he's attempting to do.
다른 팀원들도 원청예의 의도를 이해 못 하고요
What's there to do then?
그럼 어떡해요?
The first half is coming to an end.
전반전 경기가 곧 끝납니다
The score has reached a shocking
스코어는 충격적이게도
7-0.
7 대 0입니다
Hongjing completely fell apart
훙징은 상대의 공격에
under the opponent's onslaught.
완전히 무너졌습니다
This seems like the end of the first half,
전반전이 끝난 것처럼 보이지만
yet the whole game is practically over.
사실상 경기는 이미 오래전에 끝난 것 같습니다
Wen Chengye,
원청예
why did you quit your position?
왜 자꾸 위치에서 벗어나?
If it weren't for you,
너만 아니었으면
would we have lost these many goals?
우리가 이렇게까지 실점했겠어?
What do you know?
네가 뭘 알아?
Who are you to blame me?
어디서 나한테 지적질이야?
Qin Ao, did you even see everyone's position on the pitch?
친아오 경기장 포지션은 봤어?
Didn't you
남들이 막으면
know to run when others blocked you?
피할 줄 모르냐?
You were just standing there still.
통나무처럼 거기 서 있기만 하고
Say it again, I dare you!
다시 말해 봐
Fine, might as well speak my mind.
사실이잖아
You guys
너희 같은 놈들은
turn into wimps when you play against a strong team.
강팀이랑 붙기만 하면 두부처럼 물러터져선
[Youth Football Super League]
[유소년 축구 슈퍼 리그]
You collapse at the slightest attack.
건드리기만 해도 부서져
What?
왜?
Too embarrassed to admit how you performed?
뛸 낯짝은 있고 들을 낯짝은 없냐?
Boss.
대장
Seems like you're not exhausted yet.
아직 힘이 남아도나 보네
[Youth Football Super League]
[유소년 축구 슈퍼 리그]
Wen Chengye, I'm telling you,
원청예, 잘 들어
if Coach weren't here today,
오늘 코치님만 안 계셨어도
I would beat you up
네 얼굴을 아주 작살을 내놨을 거야
to fix that foul mouth of yours.
그 더러운 주둥이까지
If you want a fight so badly,
그렇게 싸우고 싶으면
let's withdraw from the game,
차라리 기권하고
so you can brawl till there's blood!
피 터지게 싸우든가
Otherwise, save all your energy and anger
아니면 그 힘이랑 분노를 아껴 뒀다가
for the opponent.
상대한테나 쏟아부어 버려
Coach Wang is right.
코치님 말씀이 맞아
The first half just ended.
이제 막 전반전이 끝났을 뿐이야
[Youth Football Super League]
[유소년 축구 슈퍼 리그]
The second half hasn't yet started.
후반전은 시작도 안 했어
Everything is possible.
아무것도 정해진 건 없다고
But falling apart right now
하지만 여기서 쓰러지면
means we've already lost.
그게 바로 지는 건데
Will you accept that?
분하지도 않아?
Of course not!
당연히 분하죠
Alright. Keep hydrated.
그럼 다들 물 마실 사람은 물 마시고
Get some rest.
쉴 사람은 쉬면서
Conserve your energy.
체력 비축하고
Prepare to give it your al in the second half.
후반전에 전력 질주할 준비해
[Youth Football Super League]
[유소년 축구 슈퍼 리그]
Wen Chengye.
원청예
If you can't take it anymore,
못 버티겠으면
quit the second half.
후반전은 뛰지 마
[Youth Football Super League]
[유소년 슈퍼 리그]
I'm doing fine.
전 괜찮아요
Wen Chengye,
원청예
use this medicine spray.
파스 가져가서 뿌려
Taking the lead with seven scores,
헝주가 7점 차로 앞선 채
Hengjiu is on the pitch for the second half.
후반전 경기를 시작합니다
The relentless pressing in the first half
전반전 계속된 몸싸움으로
has pushed Wen Chengye's stamina
원청예 선수의 체력은
almost to its limit.
거의 한계에 다다른 것 같습니다
The second half has just begun,
후반전이 막 시작됐지만
yet he is already physically drained.
몸이 둔해지기 시작했습니다
-If one wants to crash and burn, let him. -A forward of Yongchuan clearly
- 융촨도 이점을 인지했나요? - 사서 고생하겠다는데 놔둬
noticed that and stole the ball from him.
원청예 선수의 발밑에서 공을 가로챕니다
The physical dropoff
체력 저하로
causes Wen Chengye's technical movements
원청예 선수의 기술 동작에
to break down badly.
심각한 문제가 생긴 것 같습니다
What Wen Chengye said...
원청예가 한 말...
Actually made a point.
일리가 있어요
Their strength has improved a lot,
애들 실력도 많이 늘었고
and they have tactics in mind.
전술도 알고 있어요
But once they encounter a super strong opponent,
다만 아주 강한 팀을 만나면
they lose the ability to think quickly and analytically.
빠르게 사고하는 능력을 잃어 버린 것 같아요
We've already lost, haven't we?
우리 이미 진 거죠?
Do you mind it a lot?
그렇게 신경 쓰여요?
There are ups and downs in life.
인생에도 우여곡절이 있는데
The same goes for a match.
하물며 경기야 오죽하겠어요?
It's just...
그냥...
I'm a bit reluctant to accept the result.
그냥 좀 분해서요
On the pitch, things are constantly changing.
경기장이란 게 원래 변화무쌍한 법이죠
A pre-planned formation doesn't always work.
미리 짜 놓은 진영이 항상 통하는 건 아니에요
In the face of sheer strength,
절대적인 실력 앞에서는
all tactics are futile.
어떤 전술도 소용없거든요
Before surpassing Yongchuan Hengjiu,
융촨 헝주를 넘어서려면
our players still have a long way to go.
아직 갈 길이 멀어요
What you're saying
그렇게 말하니까
sounds a bit fatalistic.
운명론자처럼 들리네요
That's not what I mean.
그런 뜻이 아니라
On the contrary,
오히려
I respect our players' hard work.
전 애들의 노력을 존중해요
However, football is a team sport.
다만 축구는 팀 스포츠인데
Now, there's already little teamwork left in them.
지금 애들한테 협동심이 전혀 안 보이거든요
The players of Hongjing are having trouble coordinating
훙징의 후방 플레이에
with each other in the defensive half.
문제가 좀 있어 보입니다
The team's execution and cohesion are both declining.
실행력과 응집력이 모두 떨어지고 있습니다
Yongchuan Hengjiu just scored another goal,
융촨 헝주가 한 골 더 넣습니다
extending their lead to 9-0.
점수는 9 대 0으로 벌어졌습니다
Hengjiu's on a great momentum,
헝주는 갈수록 순조롭지만
while Hongjing's defensive formation
훙징의 수비 진영은
has completely fallen apart.
완전히 무너졌습니다
Yongchuan Hengjiu launches a long pass again as a counterattack.
융촨 헝주가 다시 롱패스로 역습을 시도합니다
-Let me take this! -Hongjing's No. 10, Fu Xinshu, and No. 11,
- 훙징의 푸신수와 원청예가 - 내가 할게
Wen Chengye, sprint at the same time.
동시에 점프하는데요
The two of them collide,
두 선수가 부딪혔습니다
but neither can touch the ball!
하지만 둘 다 공을 건드리지 못하고
An opportunity opens for Hengjiu.
헝주에게 기회가 왔습니다
They scores another goal!
한 골 더 넣습니다
Bravo!
잘했어
Boys,
얘들아
-Fu!
- 푸신수
Look, there was a foul.
저거 반칙 아냐?
-Are you okay, Fu?
- 푸신수, 괜찮아?
-Hongjing's No. 10 appears badly injured. -Is it the ankle?
- 심각한 부상으로 보입니다 - 발목 돌아간 거야?
-Medics have entered the pitch. -Fu Xinshu!
- 팀 닥터가 들어옵니다 - 푸신수
They're quickly attending to the player.
신속하게 선수의 부상을 처리하고 있습니다
-Are you okay? -The right foot, huh?
- 괜찮니? - 오른발이지?
My foot...
발이...
Hold still.
움직이지 마라
Don't move.
함부로 움직이면 안 돼
-Qin! -Qin Ao!
- 친아오
-You did it on purpose, didn’t you?
- 원청예, 일부러 그랬지?
Talk later. The game's still on.
지금 경기 중이잖아
Qin Ao,
친아오
don't be like this.
그러지 마
Right, I did that on purpose.
그래, 일부러 그랬다
-So what? -Qin Ao!
- 왜 그래? - 친아오
Apologize,
사과해
right now!
지금 당장!
You're on a football field.
지금 경기 중이야
All of you, shut up!
다들 가만있어
Coach of Hongjing,
훙징팀 코치님
can the team captain continue with the game?
팀 주장이 계속 뛸 수 있겠습니까?
Coach, I'm feeling much better after the ice spray.
코치님, 방금 스프레이 뿌려서 괜찮아진 것 같아요
I can continue with the game.
계속 뛸게요
-Don't move. -Stay still.
- 일단 가만있어 - 움직이지 마
For this match,
이제
the injured player Fu Xinshu is leaving the field.
부상당한 푸신수는 빠지고
The rest of the players will finish the game.
나머지 선수들로 경기를 끝까지 뛸 겁니다
will finish the game!
나머지 선수들이 경기를 끝까지 뛴다
Alright, let's go.
그래, 가자
Go.
가자
Be careful.
조심해
Pass it to me!
나한테 패스
After what you did to Fu,
네가 푸신수를 망친 것도 모자라서
you want me to pass the ball to you now?
이제 와서 나한테 패스해 달라고?
In your dreams!
꺼져
Ten players against eleven.
10명이 11명을 상대하고
Trailing by ten goals.
10골이나 뒤처진 상황인데요
I've never seen a game
제 해설 경력에서
like this in my entire career.
오늘 같은 경기는 처음 보는 것 같습니다
Pass it forward!
앞으로 넘겨
There's a window!
찬스다
[Hongjing No. 8 High School versus Yongchuan Hengjiu] [0-11]
[훙징 제8고등학교 00] [융촨 헝주 11]
The game is over.
경기가 종료됐습니다
The final score is 11-0.
최종 스코어 11 대 0으로
Yongchuan Hengjiu crushed Hongjing No. 8 High School!
융촨 헝주가 훙징 제8고를 상대로 압승을 거뒀습니다
♪ There's nothing to fear ♪
♪ 두려울 게 없어 ♪